How confident are you that AI's promise will outweigh the perils?
I'm not confident, but that's what we need to get oriented around.
That's why I was surprised AI wasn't really an issue in the last election.
It's definitely got to be shaped.
Hearing you say you're not confident is kind of scary.
People should think through how is AI going to reshape our lives.
It is a profound change agent.
And, you know, I don't think it should just be the people who know the technology because there's a lot of choices about how it gets used.
It will change learning.
It will change the job market.
And, you know, I think we can shape that in the right way.
But it'll be, you know, just like nuclear energy, nuclear weapons.
It'll challenge us.